A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial Press Office, Series 3 FA456
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Gubernatorial Press Office, 3; 10.8 Cubic Feet 9 record storage cartons.
  - Honeyoe Falls, NY, 1008.15/Roll810F-G (Box 6)
    - At Empire State Potato Field Day Honeyoe Falls (Box 6)
      - Governor greets Mrs. Brian Snyder of Albion NY, at left is Mrs. Wickham (Roll 810G, Frame 5)
      - unidentified at Honeyoe Falls (Roll 810G, Frame 7)
      - Governor talks to C.D. Ward of Rochester NY (Roll 810G, Frame 8)
      - Governor and LT. Governor Wilson with birthday cake for Jerry Fennessy (Roll 810G, Frame 9-10)
      - Lt Governor, Governor, and Don Wickham at Fireman's refreshment stand, at right is Howard A Stanley of Mendon, NY (Roll 810G, Frame 11-12)
      - Governor with George Tolcott, Supervisor, Spafford NY, (left) and Richard Ameda of La Fayette, NY (Roll 810G, Frame 13)
      - Lt. Governor Wilson, Vincent Toffney (?) and Governor (Roll 810G, Frame 14)
      - Unidentified man, Governor, and Donald Shoemaker (Roll 810G, Frame 15)
      - Governor with Donald Shoemaker, Assemblyman of Webster NY (Roll 810G, Frame 16)
      - Governor with Arthur McDermott of Genoa NY and Don Howard of Canandaigua NY (Roll 810G, Frame 17)
      - Governor greets four year old Billie Stone of De Witt NY, Mrs. Stone also in picture (Roll 810G, Frame 18)
      - Governor greets spectators at Honeyoe Falls (Roll 810G, Frame 19)
  - Canandaigua, NY, 1008.15/Roll810H; (23) (Box 6)
    - Governor arrives at the Ontario County Republican parade on rides in parade to picnic (Roll 810H, Frame 1-7)
    - Governor with Fred Dugan and his family (Roll 810H, Frame 8-9)
    - Governor with County Chairman Tom Allen (Roll 810H, Frame 10)
    - Fred Dugan, Governor and Tom Allen (Roll 810H, Frame 11-12)
    - Governor greets James Vogt (back to camera) (Roll 810H, Frame 13)
    - Governor rides old stagecoach at the Ontario County Rep. picnic (Roll 810H, Frame 14-20)
    - Governor speaks at the Ontario County picnic (Roll 810H, Frame 21-23)
  - Glens Falls, NY, 1966 August 11; 1008.15/Roll811A-C (Box 6)
    - Governor Rockefeller at Glens Falls. Lake George and Saratoga, 1966 August 11; 1008.15/Roll811A-C (Box 6)
      - Governor on arrival at Glens Falls Airport, met by local Republican leaders Etc (Roll 811A, Frame 1-4)
      - Governor with Donal Winchel, President Glens Falls, Typo Union and his children Stevon and Dobbie of Glens Falls, NY (Roll 811A, Frame 5)
      - Governor with Al Hamel, Secretary of Labor Trade Council (Roll 811A, Frame 6)
      - Governor with young New Yorkers at Glens Falls (Roll 811A, Frame 7-8)
      - Governor speaks at Glens Falls Rotary Club Luncheon (Roll 811A, Frame 9-11)
      - Dr William Bitner, President Glens Falls Rotary Club & Governor (Roll 811A, Frame 12)
      - Assemblyman Larry Corbett and Governor (Roll 811A, Frame 13)
      - Assemblyman Corbett, Miss Louise Schiavone of Hudson Falls, NY and Governor and Dick Bartlett (Roll 811A, Frame 14)
      - Governor, Dick Bartlett, and A.S. Knight, Publisher, Lake George Mirror (Roll 811A, Frame 15)
      - Don Morris of Glens Falls and Governor (Roll 811A, Frame 16)
      - at Lake George State Park Beach (Roll 811A, Frame 17-20)
      - Governor with local Rep. VIPs (Roll 811A, Frame 21)
      - New York (see roll 811B 1-2) (Roll 811A, Frame 22-23)
      - Governor with daughters of Mr. and Mrs. Berge Dardiarian of Tuckahoe, NY Linda 3 and Christine 5 (Roll 811B, Frame 1-5)
      - Governor on beach with youngsters (Roll 811B, Frame 6-13)
      - lifeguards with Governor: Howard MacDonald of Lake George, Michael Mastrianni of Glens Falls and Jerry Richin (on chair) of Lake George (Roll 811B, Frame 14-15)
      - Governor gives autograph to Miss Diane Morriseey, 33 Second Ave. S. Glens Falls (Roll 811B, Frame 16)
      - Governor with Edmund Moran, Ticonderoga (President NYS. Conservation Council) (Roll 811B, Frame 17)
      - Governor arrives at Teen Age Republican School of Politics at Skidmore College, Saratoga NY (Roll 811B, Frame 18-20)
      - Ovation by teenagers, etc. (Roll 811B, Frame 21)
      - Governor and Skidmore College President (Roll 811B, Frame 22)
      - Governor at Teenage Rep. School at Skidmore College (Roll 811C, Frame 1-2)
      - Governor with Andrew Rosenblatt of Hicksville, LI, NY who was chosen outstanding TAR of 1966 (Roll 811C, Frame 2-7)
      - Mrs. Charles Knauss, Dir of TARs and Governor (Roll 811C, Frame 8)
      - same as 2-7 and unidentified woman (Roll 811C, Frame 9)
      - Governor leaves TAR ceremony (Roll 811C, Frame 10-11)
      - Governor arrives at Saratoga Rep. county Com. Reception at Gidoon Putnam Hotel (Roll 811C, Frame 12)
      - Governor with local candidates Fred Davis (Assembly) Douglas Hudson (Senate) (Roll 811C, Frame 13-15)
  - Latin American Baseball, 1966 August 13; 1008.15/Roll813A; (15) (Box 6)
    - Brenda Salgado, Bexaida Perez, Evelyn Colon, Julita Gonzolez (Roll 813A, Frame 1)
    - Carraco, Rocky, Dominican Republic (Roll 813A, Frame 3)
    - Irving Linares, Tony Perez, Gonzalo Placencia, Eusebio Martinez, Lefkowitz, Rocky, Rene Roble (Shorty Batista), Commissioner Ruperto Ruiz (Roll 813A, Frame 11)
    - Marcial Quinones, Jr., Marcial Quinones, Sr., Tony Perez, Julio Hernandez, Esuebio Martinez, Ramon Rosado, Rocky, Jabao Quesada, Tono Reyes, Richard Pagan, Rene Robles, Jose Obregon (Roll 813A, Frame 16)
    - Raymond Vega, Rocky, Zoraida Martinez, Irma Martinez, Mercedes Dulco (Roll 813A, Frame 18)
  - Playland (Box 6)
    - Roll 813B, 1008.15/Roll813B; (23)
    - Roll 813C, 1008.15/Roll813C; (24) (Box 6)
    - Roll 813D, 1008.15/Roll813D; (16) (Box 6)
    - Roll 813E, 1008.15/Roll813E; (30)
    - Roll 813F, 1008.15/Roll813F; (10) (Box 6)
  - Middletown, NY, Orange County Republican Committee Festival, 1966 August 14; 1008.15/Roll814A-814D (Box 6)
    - Governor greets Candidate for Assembly William Gilman as he arrives at the festival (Roll 814A, Frame 1)
    - Governor autographing at the festival, Louis V Mills Congressional Candidate at left and William Gillman, Assembly candidate at right (Roll 814A, Frame 2)
    - Left to Right, Louis V mills, unidentified man, Governor and William Gilman (Roll 814A, Frame 3)
    - Governor waves to crowd at festival (Roll 814A, Frame 4)
    - Governor meets beauty contest contestants (Roll 814A, Frame 5-6)
    - Governor with Mrs. Carpenter and Mrs. Ida (Roll 814A, Frame 7-8)
    - Governor speaking at the festival (Roll 814A, Frame 9-12)
    - Governor with Young Republican workers (Roll 814B, Frame 1)
    - Governor with Louis V Mills, Candidate for Congress (Roll 814B, Frame 2)
    - Governor greeting several of the crowd (Roll 814B, Frame 3)
    - Governor with three year old Laurie Lucas of Campbell hall NY (Roll 814B, Frame 4-5)
    - Governor watches bandleader (Roll 814B, Frame 10-11)
    - Governor greets members of the county Rep. Club (Roll 814C, Frame 1)
    - Governor with beauty contestants (Roll 814C, Frame 2-5)
    - Governor with 1965 beauty contest winner (Roll 814C, Frame 6)
    - Governor with two of the beauty contestants (Roll 814C, Frame 7)
    - Governor and Carl Spad (Roll 814C, Frame 8)
    - Governor copter leaving (Roll 814C, Frame 9)
    - The Governor speaking at the festival, mingling with the crowd and listening to local training school band, 35 mm negatives (Roll 814D)
  - Elmira, NY and Chemung County Fair and Opening of HQ in Buffalo, 1966 August 16-17; 1008.15/Roll816B-816G (Box 7)
    - Governor at Elmira Airport on way to Chemung County Fair (Roll 816B, Frame 1-2)
    - Governor Rockefeller greets Chataye O'Loughlin - 5 y/o of Watkins Glen, NY (Roll 816B, Frame 3)
    - Governor Rockefeller greets Steven Smith, Schuyler County head-Start pupil (Roll 816B, Frame 4)
    - Governor with Caroline and Marjorie Lant of Horsehead, NY and ribbons won by their cattle (Roll 816C, Frame 1)
    - Gove with Bill Yearsley of Waverly, NY and his champion Hereford cow (Roll 816C, Frame 2-5)
    - Kenneth Dawes of Horsehead, and Governor, Brown Swiss Calf (Roll 816C, Frame 6-7)
    - Governor with glass of milk at 4H refreshment booth (Roll 816C, Frame 8)
    - Governor presents Science Award to Dale Utter, 13 y/o, Sing Sing Rd, Horsehead, NY Pres of Airport Angels 4H Club at left is leader of club, Frank Johnson (Roll 816C, Frame 9-10)
    - Gove with Mrs. Ethel Slater of Millport, NY at homemaking booth (Roll 816C, Frame 11)
    - Governor is given honorary membership in Chemung County Soil and Water Conservation group by Robert Erway, Pres (Roll 816C, Frame 12)
    - Governor at Chemung county Co-operative Extension Booth, L to R are: Senator William T Smith, Governor, Mrs. Sara Wolcott (home demonstration agent) Mr. Robert Boehleche (Chairman) (Roll 816C, Frame 13)
    - Governor with Mrs. Isabelle Upson, of Millport, NY (Roll 816C, Frame 14)
    - Governor with Mrs. Grace Thiel of Elmira NY, Mrs. Bertha Brown of Horsehead, NY at Senior Citizens Booth (Roll 816C, Frame 15)
    - Governor and Mrs. Hazel Sweet with school lunch exhibit, she is of Horsehead J.H.S. Horsehead, NY (Roll 816C, Frame 16)
    - L to R: Senator W.T. Smith, Charles Anderson and Bob Turner, Secy, of Fair (Roll 816C, Frame 17)
    - Governor at Republican Booth at Elmira Fair (Roll 816C, Frame 18-21)
    - At Republican Booth with local VIPs (Roll 816D, Frame 1-3)
    - Governor with 80 y/o Dan Hungerford of Elmira (Roll 816D, Frame 4)
    - Governor with Mrs. Elizabeth Punzo, Mrs James Castonza and Mrs. Albert Baccile of Italian American Club of Elmira (Roll 816D, Frame 5)
    - Governor meets Beauty Contest contestants (Roll 816D, Frame 6)
    - Governor with Sheba, 11 y/o elephant of Remo Cristiani, girl is Irene Cristiani. (Roll 816D, Frame 7-12)
    - Governor with mare and pony of Nancy Wladis of Elmira (left) and holding pony is Carol Christian, of Elmira, NY (Roll 816D, Frame 13)
    - Governor with Dick Ring of Horsehead, NY and his grand champion stallion (Roll 816D, Frame 14)
    - Governor congratulates Jean Graner of Elmira, NY on winning blue ribbon (Roll 816D, Frame 15)
    - Governor with Debbie Bannister of Horsehead, NY and her pony (Roll 816D, Frame 16)
    - Governor with Trooper E R Stuart and Sgt. W D Taylor of NYS. Police, Horsehead (Roll 816D, Frame 17)
    - Arrives at Buffalo Airport, Leaves Plane (Roll 816D, Frame 18)
    - Governor greets Mrs. James Kelly, Erie County Vice Chairman. Ray Lawley, county Chairman in picture (Roll 816D, Frame 19)
    - Governor and Ray Lawley (Roll 816D, Frame 20)
    - At the opening of western NYS. Rockefellers Headquarters, Buffalo, NY (Roll 816E, Frame 1-12)
    - Presenting flowers to Mrs. Rockefeller - are left - Maeyann Lee of Buffalo and Kasia Wardynski of Williamsville (Roll 816F, Frame 1-2)
    - Cutting ribbon at HQ opening (Roll 816F, Frame 3)
    - Governor and Mrs. R. at opening of Western HQ (Roll 816F, Frame 4-7)
    - Mrs. R with Michelle and Lisa Hanney, daughters of Jack Hanney of Williamsville, NY (Roll 816F, Frame 8)
    - Mrs. R. receives flowers from Mrs. Richard Triple, wife of Amherst Town Chairman (Roll 816F, Frame 9)
    - At Reception for Community Leaders at Statler hotel (Box 7)
      several blanks at start of roll
      - Herbert Nunez with Governor at the town of Amherst Rep. Com. Party (Roll 816G, Frame 5)
      - Governor with Adams and Haitd. (local candidates for Nov. election) Governor speaking (Roll 816G, Frame 7-10)
      - with elephant (Roll 816G, Frame 12-14)
      - Ed E. Cook, town councilman of Amherst (Roll 816G, Frame 15)
      - Speaking at Jewish leaders breakfast (Roll 816G, Frame 16-17)
      - Governor with Howard Saperstein and his son Howard Jr. (Roll 816G, Frame 19)
      - Governor with Paul P. Cohen, of Buffalo, NY (Roll 816G, Frame 20)
      - Governor with Paul Doseberg, Erie County Chairman, Associate of Rockefeller Team and Sam Hausman Sate Chairman, Association for Rockefeller (Roll 816G, Frame 21)
  - Buffalo, NY, 1966 August 17; 1008.15/Roll817A; (20) (Box 7)
    - Governor at Church Leader breakfast at hotel Statler (Roll 817A, Frame 1-5)
    - Governor and Rev Mitchell and Rev Sandy Ray (Roll 817A, Frame 6)
    - Governor arrives to speak at Independent Order of Odd Fellows of State of NY Convention at Hotel Statler (Roll 817A, Frame 7)
    - Governor with unidentified man as he arrived at 100F Meeting (Roll 817A, Frame 8)
    - Governor at 100F Meeting (Roll 817A, Frame 9)
    - Governor is greeted by Carl W Boltz, Grand Master of 100F (Roll 817A, Frame 10)
    - (L to R) Louis R Patur, incoming Grand Master, Florence Burns, Governor Rockefeller and Carl W Boltz, Grand Master (Roll 817A, Frame 11)
    - At 100 F. Meeting. Governor congratulates incoming Grand Master, Louis Patur (at right) is Grand Master Carl W Boltz (Roll 817A, Frame 12)
    - Governor speaks at 100F Meeting (Roll 817A, Frame 13)
    - Governor with Ray Lawler at Statler Hilton (Roll 817A, Frame 14-15)
    - On arrival at Niagara Hotel, Niagara Falls for meeting of Polish Union of American Meeting (Roll 817A, Frame 18-19)
    - Governor with Professor Joseph Slawinski, of Buffalo NY, and State Sen. Earl Brydges (Roll 817A, Frame 20)
    - Same as #20 with addition at left of Mrs. Walter Jarzab of Niagara Falls (Roll 817A, Frame 21)
    - Governor speaking at Polish Union Meeting - State Sen. Earl Brydges at left, Henry Osinski at right (Roll 817A, Frame 22)
    - Group of Polish people and Governor (Roll 817A, Frame 23)
  - Niagara Falls, 1008.15/Roll817B; (20) (Box 7)
    - Governor: autographs after Polish Meeting (Roll 817B, Frame 1-3)
    - Governor with group of Polish person (Roll 817B, Frame 4)
    - Governor with State Sen. Earl Brydges (Roll 817B, Frame 5)
    - Governor with Republican volunteer workers outside Niagara Hotel (Roll 817B, Frame 6-7)
  - Henrietta. NY, Monroe County Fair, 1008.15/Roll817B-817C; (10) (Box 7)
    - At Henrietta, NY (Roll 817B)
      - Governor at Monroe County Airport, Rochester, NY greeted by local republicans (Roll 817B, Frame 8-10)
      - Governor greets Miss Trudie Brower of Spencerport, NY (Roll 817B, Frame 14)
    - At Monroe County Fair, Henrietta, NY (Roll 817B)
      - Governor with Mark Cuer, of Hilton, NY (Roll 817B, Frame 15)
      - Governor with 16 y/o (Roll 817B, Frame 16)
      - Timmy Foster, 85 Aldrich Rd. Fairport, NY and Janice Ellsworth of Fairport, NY (Roll 817B, Frame 17)
      - Governor and Marianne Morey, 646 Cumberland Way, Webster, NY (Harvest Queen of the Fair, and Diane Legge, 31 Arlington Drive, Pittsford, NY, with day old calf of John A Gay, Churchville, NY (Roll 817B, Frame 18-19)
      - Governor greets Darlene Liebeck of Churchville, NY, as she sits on cow of John Kuszlyk of Palmer Rd, Churchville, NY (he is partially hidden by Governor) (Roll 817B, Frame 20)
      - Governor gets hamburger from Mrs. Mabel Sattel of Greece NY and R. W. Thorne of Brookveiw Dr., Rochester, 23 NY at Grange Refreshment booth (Roll 817B, Frame 22)
      - Governor eats at Grange Refreshment Booth (Roll 817B, Frame 23)
      - Governor with campaigning calf of Glen Trie (Roll 817B, Frame 21)
    - At the Monroe Country Republican Booth (Roll 817C, Frame 1)
    - Governor with Morley Schloss and Gray Brown at Liberty Party Booth (Roll 817C, Frame 2)
    - At the Monroe Country Republican Booth (Roll 817C, Frame 3)
    - Governor gets maple syrup from Edward Reynolds (Roll 817C, Frame 4)
    - Governor at Town Republican Booth (Roll 817C, Frame 5-7)
    - Governor with Sgt. Charles Mouser (Roll 817C, Frame 8)
    - Governor greets Red Cross worker (Roll 817C, Frame 9)
    - Governor thanks Trooper J.B Kontabecki and Sgt, C C Zink of NYS. police, Henrietta, NY (Roll 817C, Frame 10)
  - Camp Smith, 1966 August 19 (Box 7)
    - Governor Rockefeller at Schenectady, NY and Altamont Fair, 1966 August 19; 1008.15/Roll819A-819G, 820A (Box 7)
      - Governor at Dedication and Review of Camp Smith - graduation exercises of Empire State military Academy Officer Candidate School (Roll 819A)
        - Governor Rockefeller with Major General A C O'Hara Governor greets award winning member of the Guard-Gen. (Roll 819A, Frame 1-2)
        - Sgt. E5 Richard H. Scheels (Roll 819A, Frame 3)
        - Sgt. E5 Edwin B. Harnish Jr (Roll 819A, Frame 4)
        - Sgt. E5 Christopher G. Staff (Roll 819A, Frame 5)
        - Pfc. Harold J. McClellan (Roll 819A, Frame 6)
        - Troops pass in review (Roll 819A, Frame 8)
        - Graduating class (Roll 819A, Frame 9)
      - Governor visits Camp Smith, NY, 9/19/1966 (Roll 819B)
        - Troops are sworn in by Governor (print for Gen. O'Hara) (Roll 819B, Frame 1)
        - Governor at Gen. O'Hara's quarters (Roll 819B, Frame 2-3)
      - Governor Rockefeller at Buffalo Airport to meet President Johnson (Roll 819D)
        - Governor greets spectators awaiting President Johnson (Roll 819D, Frame 1-3)
        - Governor in vicinity of President & Mrs. Johnson (Roll 819D, Frame 4)
          see Roll 819C-35 mm
        - Governor greets Buffalo Motorcycle Police escort members (Roll 819D, Frame 5)
        - Governor with State police Major Don Crandon, NYS. Police, Albany, Maj. John Nohlan of NYS. Police, Batavia, NY, First Sgt. M. W. Wilmoth of NYS. Police, Batavia, NY (Roll 819D, Frame 6)
      - Governor on Arrival at Schenectady Airport. Plane (F27) in background as he speaks (Roll 819E, Frame 1-3)
      - At Altmount Fair
        - Greeted by crowd on arrival at Fair (Roll 819E, Frame 4-5)
        - Governor with B. B. Piatt, of Jackson, N.J. (Roll 819E, Frame 6)
        - Governor in crowd at Fair (Roll 819E, Frame 7-8)
        - Governor with unidentified children at Fair (Roll 819E, Frame 9-10)
      - Governor with Julie Dykemans, of Delanson, NY (Roll 819F, Frame 1-3)
      - With Junior Championship Ayrshire and Grand Champion Milking Shorthorn (Roll 819F, Frame 4)
      - Governor with group of children (Roll 819F, Frame 5)
      - Governor with John Geurtze, of Glenmont NY (Roll 819F, Frame 6-7)
      - Governor eats frankfurter, at left is Mary Lou Bloodgood (Roll 819F, Frame 8)
      - Mrs. Bob Douglas and child (Roll 819F, Frame 9-10)
      - Governor eats at Glenorable Grange Booth (Roll 819F, Frame 11-12)
      - Unidentified (Roll 819G, Frame 1)
      - Governor with Bob Douglas (Roll 819G, Frame 2-4)
      - Governor with Andy Halversen and his daughter (Roll 819G, Frame 5-7)
      - Mrs. Mildred Massoth (Roll 819G, Frame 8)
      - Governor with Science award winners, from L to R, Linda Berk of Hoofbeach and Clatter 4H Club, Cheryl Krenzier of Hilltop 4H Club, Schenectady, Alice Hanson of Chatter 4H Club, Delmar, Patty Crisafulli of Jolly Homemakers 4H Club, Selkirk (Roll 819G, Frame 9)
      - Governor with another group of award winners - Sharan Chriss of Amsterdam, NY, Orson Bellamy- Patron of Glenville Jr. Grange, Mrs. Betty Clark, Glenridge Jr. Grange, Scotia, NY Matron, Mrs Helen Raynor of Hiawatha Jr. Grange, R'ville, NY (Roll 819G, Frame 10)
      - Sheila Jordan of Altamont, NY pins flower on Governor's lapel (Roll 819G, Frame 11)
      - unidentified (Roll 820A, Frame 1)
      - Governor with youngster who escorted him through Altamont Fair, names to come from Fred Hart (Roll 820A, Frame 2)
      - Governor with Clayton Ackles of Clinton Comm. who presented carved elephant (Roll 820A, Frame 3)
  - New York City, 1966 August 22; 1008.15/Roll822A-822G (Box 7)
    - At. VFW Convention - Hotel Hilton Governor with NYS. Commander Herbert, Brian and other members of VFW (Roll 822A, Frame 1-3)
    - Governor is escorted to the Platform (Roll 822A, Frame 4)
    - Governor speaking at VFW conv (Roll 822A, Frame 5)
    - Governor with National commander, Andy Borg (Roll 822A, Frame 6-9)
    - Governor presented flag by Auxiliary (Roll 822A, Frame 7-8)
    - Unidentified (Roll 822A, Frame 10)
    - At Radio and TV interview (Roll 822A, Frame 11)
    - Governor with Two women volunteers per H O'Donnell (Roll 822B, Frame 1-2)
    - Governor at Store Front opening 22-47 31st St Astoria, LI (Roll 822B, Frame 3-8)
    - Governor cuts ribbon at entrance to store opening, above (Roll 822B, Frame 9)
    - Governor walking along 82nd St. Jackson Heights (Roll 822C, Frame 1-2)
    - Governor Greets Meter Maid Mrs. Louise Racy (Roll 822C, Frame 3)
    - Governor greets Con Ed worker (Roll 822C, Frame 4-6)
    - Governor speaks at store opening 37-47 82nd St Jackson Heights (Roll 822C, Frame 7-8)
    - Governor with 3 sisters (Roll 822D, Frame 1-2)
    - Governor cuts ribbon at Jackson Heights store front (Roll 822D, Frame 3)
    - Governor at Jackson Heights store (Roll 822D, Frame 4)
    - Governor at 1312 Fulton St, Brooklyn Store Front opening (Roll 822D, Frame 5-11)
    - At store front opening 1312 Fulton St. Brooklyn (Roll 822E, Frame 1-2)
    - Governor with Mrs. Rebecca Hall (Roll 822E, Frame 3)
    - Governor with Lionel Hampton (Roll 822E, Frame 4-5)
    - Governor at Store Front opening 168-06 Hillside Ave Jamaica, LI (Roll 822E, Frame 7-10)
    - Governor with Charles Viscoits 219-11 Hillside Ave, opening Hillside Ave front (Roll 822F, Frame 1)
    - Governor at Rally 168th St Jamaica Ave at Garden City Hotel (Roll 822F, Frame 3-8)
    - Governor greets Miss Linda Olbers, Wantagh, LI (Roll 822F, Frame 9)
    - Governor with Alex Mattei (Roll 822F, Frame 10)
    - Governor speaks at Press conf Garden City Hotel (Roll 822G, Frame 1)
    - Governor with Miss Sherrylynn Armbruster (Miss NY) (Roll 822G, Frame 2-4)
    - Governor at Young New Yorkers Meeting (Roll 822G, Frame 5-6)
    - At Nassau County Republican Workers Reception Garden City (Roll 822G, Frame 7-12)
  - Franklin County, NY, 1966 August 23; 1008.15/Roll823B; (12) (Box 7)
    - At Franklin County Fair (Box 7)
      - Governor meets Mrs. Roderick Noreault of Merrill, NY and her children Winona and Noell (Roll 823B, Frame 1)
      - Governor with eight y/o Diane Chapman (Roll 823B, Frame 2-3)
      - Governor with Mrs. Donald Cline (Roll 823B, Frame 4)
      - Governor with Mrs. William Damiere, Lake Titus, Malone, NY (Roll 823B, Frame 5)
      - Governor with unidentified children at fair (Roll 823B, Frame 6-9)
      - at Adirondack Potato Groves Booth (Roll 823B, Frame 10)
      - at Republican booth ribbon cutting (Roll 823B, Frame 11-12)
  - Malone, NY, 1008.15/Roll823A, 823C; (11) (Box 7)
    - At Malone Airport (Roll 823A)
      - Governor meets William (his grandfather help build Pocantico Bridges) (Roll 823A, Frame 1)
      - Governor with Susan Mount of Fort Covington, NY (Roll 823A, Frame 2)
      - governor and State Senator Stafford with Labor Leaders (Roll 823A, Frame 3-4)
      - Governor and Kelly Harris, daughter of Geln Harris, Assembly Candidate of Canada Lake, NY (Roll 823A, Frame 5)
      - Governor at Hotel Flanigan with young Republican (Roll 823A, Frame 6)
      - Governor - James Mills (left) and unidentified VIP (Roll 823A, Frame 7)
      - Governor - Mitchell C Jackley and Congressman Robert Mc (Roll 823A, Frame 8)
      - Governor views Huckleberry Lake Project (Roll 823A, Frame 9)
      - Governor with Kathy Moore and Kevin Prufer (Roll 823A, Frame 10)
    - Governor meets 89 y/o Mrs. Edward of Slatersville, RI. In center is Mrs. William Johnson of Burke, NY (Roll 823C, Frame 1)
    - Governor with Mrs. Francis L. LeClair (Roll 823C, Frame 2)
    - Governor with Orville McKnight of Mt View NY at Franklin County Historical Soc booth (Roll 823C, Frame 3)
    - Governor at Amvets Booth, in picture are Mrs. Marian Casazza and Commander Wesley Reynolds (Roll 823C, Frame 5-6)
    - Governor with local candidates (Roll 823C, Frame 7-8)
    - Governor autographs leg cast of Kevin Legacy of Burke, NY also in picture are father and mother Mr. & Mrs. Robert Legacy and other youngsters, Nancy and Keith (Roll 823C, Frame 9)